[
    {
        "udp": "1.1",
        "question": "Hello, Tactica",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9611.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.1",
        "question": "Hello, Tektika",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9611.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.2",
        "question": "Zoom into the UAE.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11256.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial ports in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/3_scenario_1_maltida.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial quotes in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/3_scenario_1_maltida.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial pots in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/3_scenario_1_maltida.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Khalifa Port Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15537.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Khalifa Port Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15537.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Kalifaport Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15537.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.5",
        "question": "For the ships currently here, What is their  vessel movement for the last 24 hours?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8798.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the port itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4502.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the pot itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4502.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the pod itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4502.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Enhance the optical imagery and detect all ships",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5676.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Inhale the optical imagery and detect all shapes.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5676.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What assets are in the port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What acids are in the pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What acids are in the port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What assets are in the pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.9",
        "question": "How many staff and visitors are within the port area?  ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12417.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.10",
        "question": "What is the water depth in the port area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15544.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.11",
        "question": "Provide a 3D visualization of the port's underwater topography",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10336.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": -2,
        "question": "Alert",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18747.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.12",
        "question": "Yes, get the image",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1228.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.13",
        "question": "What is the latest known information about this ship?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15160.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.14",
        "question": "What is the trajectory of this ship?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9890.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.15",
        "question": "Open and analyse the new image\nDetect and identify the ships new location and any other suspected activity of the ship",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8993.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.16",
        "question": "Generate a report on these two ships and send it to Khalid",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2850.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.17",
        "question": "Yes. Also open the report.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11829.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.18",
        "question": "Close the report.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10241.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.19",
        "question": "Yes,  Lets look at the urban areas of Abu Dhabi, Zoom into Khalifa City and do land cover classification.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9865.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.20",
        "question": "What are the newly constructed buildings in Khalifa City in 2024?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3670.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.21",
        "question": "How many vehicles are in the imagery in this area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_300.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.22",
        "question": "Identify all palm trees in the region and surrounding main roads.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1996.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.23",
        "question": "Run red weevil analysis on the palm trees.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10697.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.24",
        "question": "What is the current traffic density around the region?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1297.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.25",
        "question": "Zoom into Zayed airport?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17377.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.26",
        "question": "Identify all airplanes and what is their operational activity.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11196.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.27",
        "question": "Identify all A380 airplanes in the airport.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12028.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.28",
        "question": "Zoom into the one connected to the terminal.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13431.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.29",
        "question": "Run model logic analysis on the airplane.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18691.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.30",
        "question": "Generate a 3D of the Airbus A380",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16419.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.31",
        "question": "Do you have high frequency imagery over the airport?  ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19300.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.32",
        "question": "What are the changes in the western runway over the last 1 hour",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12377.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.33",
        "question": "Put and explain the thermal imagery.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14721.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.34",
        "question": "Standby",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15823.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.35",
        "question": "What kind of data can the system support? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17461.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.36",
        "question": "Open the notification tab",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17452.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.2",
        "question": "Tactica, generate and zoom-in into an area of interest 900 kilometers  West to East by 350 kilometers North to South, centered over the Straits of Hormuz",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16899.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.3",
        "question": "Identify all Naval ports, military, and dual-use airfields within the area of interest.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16863.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.3",
        "question": "Identify all Naval pots, military, and dual-use airfields within the area of interest.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16863.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.4",
        "question": "Identify all island-based fixed coastal defensive and anti-shipping installations ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3928.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.5",
        "question": "Identify and generate all fixed and mobile surface to air missile systems and aerial surveillance sites.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6016.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.6",
        "question": "Tactica, Which airfield has the most military activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2530.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.7",
        "question": "Zoom into the airport and tell me. What satellite imagery do you have over this airport? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7942.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.8",
        "question": "Using the most recent high-resolution optical image, identify all military aircraft types at this airport.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3281.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.9",
        "question": "Is it operational?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3292.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.10",
        "question": "Why is there no optical imagery from the last week?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9249.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.11",
        "question": "analyze the latest two SAR imagery ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7915.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.11",
        "question": "Analyze the latest two-star imagery.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7915.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.12",
        "question": "Generate a 3D representation of F4 Phantom. ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9657.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.13",
        "question": "What about Bandar Abbas International Airport? Identify all military airplanes there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2708.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.14",
        "question": "Can Bandar Abbas operate and house Iran\u2019s recently purchased SU-35 Flanker aircraft?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10599.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.15",
        "question": "Can you elaborate on the Shelters part?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6409.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.16",
        "question": "What are the specifications of the SU-35 Flanker?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18910.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.17",
        "question": "Is it a threat to UAE military forces if deployed from Bandar Abbas or Konarak Airports?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3370.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.17",
        "question": "The Z-TEP threat to UA military forces if deployed from Banda Abbas or Konurak Airpods.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3370.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.18",
        "question": "Where was the latest location where the SU-35 has been detected within the area of interest?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12485.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.19",
        "question": "To what rank",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13456.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.40",
        "question": "NPPAlert",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16346.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.20",
        "question": "Yes. Give more information about the NPP Alert.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12849.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.21",
        "question": "I don\u2019t know much about this location. What is BNPP?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14449.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.22",
        "question": "Show me more information about all the latest changes? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9425.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.23",
        "question": "Generate and open the report on the Power Plant.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16689.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.24",
        "question": "Close it, Label it as restricted, share it with my supervisor and archive it. Also, increase thermal coverage of the area.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7726.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.25",
        "question": "Thank you.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19617.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.26",
        "question": "Take me to Bandar Abbas Naval port and show me the imagery there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18579.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.26",
        "question": "Take me to Bandar Abbas Naval pot and show me the imagery there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18579.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1378.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this plot.?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1378.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this part.?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1378.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1378.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.28",
        "question": "Using this imagery, identify all naval ships within the naval port of Bandar Abbas",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6664.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.28",
        "question": "Using this imagery, identify all naval ships within the naval pot of Bandar Abbas",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6664.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.29",
        "question": "Using the last optical imagery,  what changes are occurring within the naval port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14477.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.29",
        "question": "Using the last optical imagery,  what changes are occurring within the naval pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14477.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.30",
        "question": "Highlight the changes using the latest SAR with listing them and if there is any abnormal activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1921.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.31",
        "question": "I am interested in the IRGC area. What military equipment is present in the IRGC area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18976.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.32",
        "question": "Zoom into the training and label each unit",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14621.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.33",
        "question": "What changes are observed in SAR and optical imagery?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13847.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.34",
        "question": "Is there any operational activity happening here? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1283.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.35",
        "question": "What are your recommendations for the departed ships?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4635.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.36",
        "question": "Identify all military ships in the last optical imagery in Area 1 and label.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11399.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.37",
        "question": "Why are these ships there?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15533.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.38",
        "question": "Zoom into the Bagheri drone ship and provide more information",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9660.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.38",
        "question": "Zoom into the Bikari drone ship and provide more information.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9660.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.39",
        "question": "Standby",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17430.mp3"
    }
]